{"questions":[{"question":"Can you prepare and cook a simple meal  without help from someone else?","hint":null,"category":"preparing food","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":0},{"label":"No","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need to use special aids or appliances to  prepare food or cook a simple meal?","hint":null,"category":"preparing food","answers":[{"label":"yes","value":2},{"label":"no","value":0}]},{"question":"Which of these best describes what you would use to cook a simple meal if you had a conventional or  microwave oven or were shown how to use them?","hint":null,"category":"preparing food","answers":[{"label":"I could  use both of them","value":0},{"label":"I could only use the conventional oven","value":0},{"label":"I could only use the microwave","value":2}]},{"question":"Do you need someone to tell you to cook and prepare a simple meal for yourself?","hint":null,"category":"preparing food","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":2},{"label":"No","value":0},{"label":"Sometimes","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need someone to supervise you or assist  you to cook and prepare a simple meal?","hint":null,"category":"preparing food","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":4},{"label":"No","value":0}]},{"question":"Can you prepare and cook food?","hint":null,"category":"preparing food","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":0},{"label":"Not at all","value":8},{"label":"Sometimmes","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need someone to help you eat and drink?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":0},{"label":"No","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you use a special aid or appliance to eat?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":2},{"label":"No","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need someone  to supervise you while you eat?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":2},{"label":"No","value":0},{"label":"Sometimes","value":0}]},{"question":"Can you cut up food on your own?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":0},{"label":"No","value":2},{"label":"Sometimes","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need to be prompted to eat food or about the amount you should eat?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":4},{"label":"No","value":0},{"label":"Sometimes","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need someone to help you use a tube to eat and drink?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":6},{"label":"No","value":0}]},{"question":"Do you need someone else to put food and drink into your mouth?","hint":null,"category":"taking nutrition","answers":[{"label":"Yes","value":10},{"label":"No","value":0}]}]}